<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stephan Jacobs</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stephan Jacobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Pictures Make Me Happy</title>
      <link>/post/satellite-pictures-make-me-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/satellite-pictures-make-me-happy/</guid>
      <description>I recently started using Downlink on my Mac and I have not been this delighted with a piece of software in quite some time!
To give you an idea, every morning when I come into the office I turn on my computer and I see something like this:
I mean, what a view!
Things I Particularly Enjoy 1. Cloud Shadows You only really see this at the very edges of the sunlight around dawn or dusk, because for the shadow of the cloud to be seen, it has to be very far from the cloud sideways (otherwise it&amp;rsquo;s hidden behing the cloud compared to the satellite).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to run both R and Python in Jupyter Lab session with Anaconda</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-run-both-r-and-python-in-jupyter-lab-session-with-anaconda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-run-both-r-and-python-in-jupyter-lab-session-with-anaconda/</guid>
      <description>So full disclosure, most (most, not all) of what I&amp;rsquo;m telling you below is based on this very helpful page from the Anaconda docs
But the point of writing this guide is to give you some other useful information along the way :)
Getting started The first thing you need to do is create a new conda environment. This basically means you have a special folder somewhere that contains a totally different set of installed packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to set up Atom to look and (sort of) behave like RStudio</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-set-up-atom-to-look-and-sort-of-behave-like-rstudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-set-up-atom-to-look-and-sort-of-behave-like-rstudio/</guid>
      <description>I love RStudio. It&amp;rsquo;s great. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really appreciate how great it was when I was just using RStudio to be honest, but when I started using Python more I missed some of its features a lot. About a year later, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally managed to (almost) duplicate its data focused interactive workflow in a well maintained IDE. That IDE is Atom
What exactly do I mean by RStudio (sort of)?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>